原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
翻译：草草 Alex  Lynn_宁  杨一勾 Giggles 肥嘟嘟
翻译：木浅  小僵僵   校对：木浅  某羽
时间轴：念念 吃土少女 Toozii
后期：斯人      总监：木浅
诉 讼 双 雄
第七季   第八集
《诉讼双雄》前情提要
我来通知你不要再骚扰我的律所
I'm here to tell you you're backing the hell off my firm.
你得签下协议
You got to sign something
声明我与此事无关
saying that I had nothing to do with this.
-我已经签好了  -现在这都是你的担子了
- I already did. - It's on you now.
想看看你未婚妻昨晚给我发的照片吗
You want to see a copy of the pictures your fiancée sent me?
她没给你发任何东西
She didn't send you anything.
我还复印了好多份  人手一份
I made copies, one for each guy in the joint.
纪念日快乐
Happy anniversary.
和一个
It's so nice to be with a man
听不懂话的男人工作一整天后
who's so thoughtful after spending all day
能和如此体贴的男人共度时光真是太好了
with a man who doesn't even know what the word means.
是指哈维
Talking about Harvey.
但如果他要求你离开你热爱的工作
If you can't even separate yourself from him
你却仍无法离开他
when he's asking you to leave a job that you love,
我只能好奇你爱的到底是不是这工作
makes me wonder if it's really the job you love after all.
但我觉得这笔钱的一部分
I was thinking maybe some of that money
可以给你女儿
might go to your daughter.
我知道你和她不来往了
I know you don't talk to her.
如果你这是耍我...
If you're playing with me on this thing--
我没有耍你  弗兰克
I'm not playing you, Frank.
你怎么又和弗兰克・加洛搅在了一起
What the hell are you doing with Frank Gallo?
瑞秋知道这事吗
Does Rachel know about this?
-不知道  -那你最好祈祷
- No. - And you better hope
加洛不会像给我留言这样
Gallo doesn't leave her a message
也去给她留言
the same way he left me one.
亚历克斯被人握住了把柄
Alex has a gun to his head.
我有个办法
I have a way out of it,
但是对迈克会有不好的影响
but there's gonna be some consequences for Mike.
哈维  还有别的办法吗
Harvey, is there any other way out of this mess?
如果有的话  我不会站在这了
If there were, I wouldn't be standing here.
你认为签下改造公司能解决问题
You think signing Reform Corps. is gonna make this go away,
他们手里有他的把柄
they have something on him.
你有一晚上的时间
Why don't you take the night and decide
来考虑你是否足够相信我  留下  还是走人
if you trust me enough to keep working here or not.
警卫递给我一张纸条
The guard gave me a letter,
那个警卫被犯人杀了
and that guard was murdered by an inmate.
-你掩盖了一场谋杀  -他们陷害我
- You covered up a murder? - They set me up.
我没有让你放下
I'm not asking you to let it go;
而是告诉你如果你不放下的后果
I'm telling you what would happen if you don't.
*看到钱  就愿意留下吃饭*
*See the money, wanna stay for your meal*
*给你太太再拿块馅饼*
*Get another piece of pie for your wife*
*所有人都想知道那感觉*
*Everybody wanna know how it feel*
*所有人都想见见那景象*
*Everybody wanna see what it's like*
*豆子馅饼我也愿吃  我不在乎*
*I'll even eat a bean pie, I don't mind*
*我和妹子忙着赚钱*
*Me and Missy is so busy, busy making money*
*好了*
*All right*
*退开点  我要跳舞*
*All step back, I'm 'bout to dance*
诉讼双雄 第七季 第八集
*美钞爵士摇摇摇*
*The greenback boogie*
-抱歉  你是谁来着  -我懂了
- I'm sorry, who's this? - I get it.
我这几天没回你电话
I haven't returned your calls for a few days.
-既然你说起来了  -我很抱歉
- Now that you mention it-- - Listen, I'm sorry.
这几天办公室情况一直很紧急
I've been totally under the gun at the office,
但现在应该脱离危险了
but I think we're out of the woods.
那你弥补我一下吧
Then how about you make it up to me
让我请你吃饭
by letting me take you out to dinner?
周四晚上
Thursday night.
我理理清楚
Let me get this straight.
我忙于工作
I get caught up with work
对我的惩罚就是你请我吃饭
and my punishment is you taking me out.
我是英国人  哈维
I'm British, Harvey.
我们大洋对岸的人做事方式不一样
We do things differently across the pond.
那我们周四见了
Then I guess I'll see you Thursday.
好啊  晚安  哈维
I guess you will. Good night, Harvey.
晚安  宝拉
Good night, Paula.
-你好  -马克  你好
- Hello? - Mark, hi.
我是唐娜・保尔森
It's Donna Paulson.
唐娜
Donna.
这...
It's, uh...
接到你的电话真好  好久没联系了
good to hear from you. It's been a long time.
是啊  我...
Yeah. I was, um--
我刚好想起了你
I was just thinking about you and I...
就决定打个电话
decided to give you a call.
那太好了
I'm--I'm glad you did.
我也会时不时想起你
You know, I think about you from time to time, too.
-好奇怪啊  -是吗
- This is weird. - Oh, I don't know.
前女友突然深夜来电
Ex-girlfriend calling, out of the blue, late night.
-我见过更怪的  -是吗
- I think I've seen weirder. - Oh, have you.
虽然现在一时想不起来
Well, nothing I can think of this second,
但我肯定见过的
but I'm sure I have.
不如在你想的时候
Well, while you're thinking about it,
顺便看看日历
why don't you check your calendar
能不能挤出点时间跟我吃顿饭
and see if you can squeeze me in for lunch sometime soon.
我不用看日历
I don't have to check my calendar.
我随时都能挤出时间见你
I'm pretty sure I can squeeze you in any time.
-那明天怎么样  -明天就不错
- Then how's tomorrow? - Tomorrow sounds good.
就去老地方
The, uh, place with the thing by the thing?
老地方就好
The place with the thing by the thing sounds good.
到时见
See you there.
你来干什么
What are you doing here?
我叫你想一晚了
I told you to take the night.
我不需要想一晚
I don't need to take the night.
我需要马上跟你谈谈
I need to talk to you right now.
如果你是来叫我放弃改造公司
If you're here to tell me to drop Reform Corp.,
-那你白来  -我不是为那个来的  哈维
- you've wasted a trip-- - I'm not here for that, Harvey.
亚历克斯什么都告诉我了
Alex told me everything.
证明给我看
Prove it.
我发誓  你要是敢用这个对付他
I swear to God, if you're gonna use this against him--
我不想拿什么对付他
I don't wanna use anything against him.
-我想帮他  -扯淡
- I wanna help him. - Bullshit.
不是扯淡  我听了他的故事
It's not bullshit. I listened to his story.
任何人都可能处于那样的境地
Anyone could've found themselves in that position.
你什么意思
So what are you saying?
我是意思是  我们本该是蝙蝠侠和罗宾的
I'm saying that you and I are supposed to be Batman and Robin, we--
要是我们不能阻止他们逍遥法外
If we can't stop these guys from getting away with it
并同时拯救亚历克斯
and save Alex in the meantime,
那我们还在干什么
then what the hell are we doing?
我猜你有计划了
I'm guessing you got a plan.
我猜我有
I'm guessing I do.
你觉得我们需要找到我们的戈登警长
You think we need to find our Commissioner Gordon.
-你怎么知道的  -因为我了解蝙蝠侠
- How'd you know that? - Because I know Batman.
我知道他需要一个内应
And I know that he needs someone on the inside
跟他在幕后合作
who's working with him behind the scenes.
瞧瞧你啊  你真的很了解蝙蝠侠
Look at you. You do know Batman.
-你有人选了吗  -当然
- You got someone in mind? - Of course I do.
除非你比你看上去得还要蠢
Unless you're even dumber than you look,
你现在也在想着这人
it's the same person you're thinking of.
罗伯特  有时间吗
Robert, you have a minute?
我有时间搞清楚你是怎么进入我家的
I got a minute to find out how you got into my house.
劳拉让我进来的
Laura let me in.
当然了
Yeah, of course she did.
她不知为何误认为你挺有魅力
She's under the misguided impression that you're charming.
告诉我你盒子里装了什么吧
Now why don't you tell me what you got in that box.
就是些文件
Just some files.
我们公司要没地方了
We were running out of space over at my firm
我想在你这儿放一些
and I thought maybe I could just store them with you.
你以为我没听说那起集体诉讼吗
You think I didn't hear about that class action?
差点搞得你们内部分裂
Just about cracked your firm in two?
我为什么要碰那玩意
Why the hell would I touch that with a ten foot pole?
罗伯特  我没有任何立场
Robert, I don't have a leg to stand on
只能说迈克接下了案子
other than to say that Mike took this on
而且发现了可怕的事实
and found some bad shit.
我要给你个机会纠正错误
I'm giving you an opportunity to right some wrongs,
赚大钱
make a shitload of money
而你只需要去参加一次会面
and all you have to do is show up for one meeting.
我这里可能还有点放东西的地方
I think I might have some extra storage space here.
但是  哈维  如果你把那些东西交给我
But, Harvey, if you leave that thing with me,
案子就是我的了  我会按自己的方式来
the case is mine and I run it how I see fit.
-这是威胁吗  -或许吧  或许不是
- Is that a threat? - Maybe it is, maybe it isn't.
但一旦我们上了场
But once we step into that ring,
我才不在乎你是谁
I don't give a shit who you are,
我是不会放水的
I'm not pulling my punches.
正合我意
I wouldn't have it any other way.
怎么回事  我以为你是我这边的
What the hell? I thought you were on my side.
我是你这边的
I am on your side.
那罗伯特・赞恩怎么突然冒出来
Then why did Robert Zane just come out of nowhere
要重启那件案子
and all of a sudden reopen that God damn case?
亚历克斯  放松
Alex, relax.
他重启不是针对你的客户
He didn't open it up against your client;
而是哈维的客户
he opened it up against Harvey's.
那有什么用
What good does that do?
他们是合伙的  我也是
They're in this thing together and so am I.
听我说  你把真相告诉了我
Listen to me. You've trusted me with the truth.
我向你保证了我不会让你为你
I gave you my word that I wouldn't let you go down
没做的事锒铛入狱
for something you didn't do.
看来你的保证一文不值
Well I guess your word is shit
因为庭审一开始
because the second this trial starts,
我背后迟早要背上靶眼
it's only a matter of time till I've got a bull's-eye on my back.
那幸好不会有庭审了
Well, then I guess it's a good thing there isn't gonna be a trial.
你说什么呢
What are you talking about?
我不能把一切都告诉你
I can't tell you everything that's going on,
但你只需要确保
but all you need to do is make sure
马斯特森建筑公司不会插手
Masterson Construction stands down.
之后  你只需要悠闲地看着整件事解决
After that, you just sit back and watch this whole thing go away.
该死
God damn it!
该死  格蕾琴
God damn it, Gretchen,
我几天前就叫你准备斯特芬妮接替人的申请了
I asked you for those applications to replace Stephanie days ago.
-在哪...  -在这里
- Where the hell-- - I have them right here.
为什么你不给我
Well, why didn't you give them to me?
因为有个问题...
Because there was a problem--
等等
Wait a second.
-感觉不对  -你怎么知道
- This doesn't feel right. - How can you know that?
因为涉及到申请  我就是天才
Because when it comes to applications, I'm like Rain Man
感觉少一份申请
and this pile feels one applicant light.
因为哥伦比亚大学选择了
That's because Columbia University
不推荐申请人
chose not to send an applicant.
为什么你不告诉我
Well, why the hell didn't you tell me?
因为这只是一个职位
Because it's one position.
我们有其它19个排名前20学校的申请  傻子
We have applications from 19 of the top 20 schools, you fool.
-你刚叫我傻子吗  -我看见就叫
- Did you just call me a fool? - I call 'em like I see 'em.
我不管其它19个怎样
Well, I don't give a shit about the other 19
即使有一个认为
if there's even one
在迈克・罗斯事件后我们不够好
that thinks we're still not good enough after Mike Ross.
我也不会坐视不管
I'm not gonna let it stand.
路易  如果你过去找麻烦
Louis, if you go over there and make trouble,
就不会只是哥大不送律师过来
it won't only be Columbia withholding lawyers from us,
而是全国的所有大学
it'll be every damn school in the country.
格蕾琴  如果你还说个没完
Gretchen, if you're gonna keep talking,
就对着我的屁股讲吧
you might as well say it to my ass
因为我现在就要过去
'cause I'm going over there right now
让他们知道谁配不上谁
to let them know who's too good for who.
-罗杰  -怎么回事
- Roger. - What the hell?
-什么怎么回事  -别装
- What the hell, what? - Don't give me that.
我做了些调查
I did a little digging.
罗伯特・赞恩就要成为迈克・罗斯的岳父了
Robert Zane is about to be Mike Ross' father-in-law
我不觉得这是个巧合
and I don't think it's a coincidence
突然间他就同一个案子找上我们
that all of a sudden, he's coming after us on the exact same case.
罗杰  我会处理的
Roger, I'll take care of it.
你最好处理  哈维
You better take care of it, Harvey.
因为我同意协议的唯一原因
Because I only signed with you
是你保证过阻止迈克・罗斯
because you promised to stop Mike Ross,
我想我不用提醒你
and I don't think I have to remind you
如果改造公司完了
that if Reform Corp. goes down,
亚历克斯・威廉姆斯就完了
Alex Williams goes down
带着你整个律所也就完了
and he takes your whole damn firm with him.
我告诉过你我会解决的
I told you. I'll take care of it.
但是你要为我做些事情
But you're gonna need to do something for me.
-是什么  -打开你的支票本
- And what is that? - Open your god damn checkbook.
罗伯特  你没必要这么和我的委托人说话
Robert, there's no cause for you to talk to my client like that.
如果你想让我邀请他喝下午茶  可以
Well, if you want me to invite him to afternoon tea, I will.
但是如果想结了这个案子
But if he wants this case to go away,
这就是他要给的金额
this is how much he's gonna have to pay.
你疯了吗
Are you out of your mind?
罗伯特  这不是和解提议
Robert, this isn't a settlement offer.
这是战书
This is a declaration of war.
那我们开战吧
Then let's go to war.
你觉得我会害怕陪审团吗
You think I'm afraid to put this in front of a jury?
你不会见到陪审团
You won't get near a jury
因为我会确保他们知道迈克・罗斯
'cause I'm gonna make sure they know Mike Ross
双手给你奉上这个案子
handed you this case on a silver platter.
你没有证据
And you don't have the proof of that
不然你不会出现在和解谈判
or you wouldn't be at a settlement meeting.
但我有证据证明
But I do have the proof
你不仅阴谋延长刑期
that you not only schemed to extend sentences,
还杀人掩盖
but murdered someone to cover it up.
你说什么
What are you talking about?
我有一个在监狱的证人
I'm talking about the fact that I have an eyewitness in prison
会出庭作证
who'll testify in court.
证人是谁
And who is this witness?
你知道他是谁
You know who he is.
而且他也知道你是谁
And he knows who you are.
除非接受我的条件
And unless you take my deal,
否则你只能等着进监狱了
you're gonna end up behind bars yourself.
我不会付这么多钱
I am not paying that kind of money
也不会承认任何事
and I am not admitting to anything.
罗杰  你听到了  他有个证人
Roger, you heard him. He has a witness.
那你最好确保弗兰克・加洛不能作证  哈维
Then you better make sure Frank Gallo doesn't testify, Harvey.
不然我就找别人
Or I'll find somebody who can.
我要和管招聘的人说话
I wanna speak to whoever the hell's in charge of recruiting
就现在
and I wanna speak to them now.
恐怕不行
Well, I'm afraid that's not possible.
不行是什么意思
What do you mean it's not possible?
你必须要预约
I mean you'll have to make an appointment.
我们不接受临时来访
We don't take in walk-ins.
我不是临时来访
Well, I'm not a walk-in.
我是路易・利特
My name is Louis Litt,
皮-斯-利律所的
from the firm Pearson Specter Litt.
-等等  你不能进去  -我可以
- Wait, you can't go in there. - Oh, yes I can.
如果你们这种人认为可以除名我们律所
If you people think you can dismiss our firm,
那你们就是疯...
you have another thing com--
-希拉  -路易
- Sheila. - Louis.
你怎么在这里
What are you doing here?
我在哥大工作六个月了
well, I've worked at Columbia for the past six months.
但你说过你绝不会离开哈佛
But you said you would never leave Harvard.
我说过  路易
I did, Louis.
-但是...  -但是什么
- But-- - But what?
我的未婚夫住在纽约  我想和他一起
My fiancé lives in the city and I wanted to be with him.
-未婚夫  -是的
- Fiancé. - Yes.
我们两周后结婚
We're getting married in two weeks.
-抱歉  路易  -你没必要道歉
- I'm sorry, Louis. - You don't need to be sorry.
我理解你为什么没有送申请
And I understand why you didn't send the applications over.
-你不想让我受伤  -是的
You didn't want me to be hurt. - I didn't.
但现在你知道了
But now that you know,
也就没有理由惩罚你或者律所了
there's no reason to punish you or the firm.
我同意
I guess not.
我会送去我们最好最聪明的学生
I'll send over our best and our brightest
确保他们知道这是一个向行业
and make sure they understand it's an opportunity
最优者学习的机会
to learn at the foot of a master.
很高兴见到你  希拉
It's good to see you, Sheila.
很高兴见到你  路易
Good to see you too, Louis.
哈维  发生了什么  他们同意了吗
Harvey, what happened? They go for it?
你背后捅刀子的岳父
What happened was your backstabbing father-in-law
毁了和解
blew up the settlement.
-什么  为什么  -因为他混蛋
- What? Why? - 'Cause he's an asshole.
现在我得阻止加洛作证
Now I gotta stop Gallo from testifying.
你在说什么
What the hell are you talking about?
我在说我要去监狱
I'm talking about going to the prison
说服那个疯子不开口
and convincing that psychopath not to talk.
-哈维  这是个坏主意  -你不明白吗
- Harvey, that's a bad idea. - Don't you get it?
他开口  亚历克斯就完了
He talks, Alex goes down.
这正是我们要避免的
That's the whole thing we're trying to avoid.
我不是说让加洛闭嘴
I'm not saying it's a bad idea
是个坏主意
to shut Gallo down.
我是说不应该你去
I'm saying that you are not the one to do it.
你疯了吗
Are you out of your mind?
你不能接近这个案子
You're not supposed to be anywhere near this case.
钥匙让改造公司听到风声...
Reform Corp. Gets wind of this--
他们能怎样  哈维
And what, Harvey?
我把对方的明星证人给搞定了
I shut down the star witness on the other side.
他们非但不生气  还会用奖牌犒劳我
They're not gonna be pissed. They're gonna give me a medal.
你凭什么认为这事你做的会比我好
What makes you think you're gonna be better at that than me?
因为  他延长刑期是因为我
Because I might've been the one who kept him there longer,
但一开始让他入狱的是你
but you-- you're the one who put him there in the first place.
你怎么来了  不是退出这案子了吗
what are you doing here? I thought you were off the case.
没错
I was.
但我又接手了
Now I'm back on.
因为我有东西要给你
'Cause I need to give you something.
好吧  什么东西
Yeah, what's this?
这笔钱要比罗伯特・赞恩
It's a hell of a lot more than whatever
雇你来作证所得的要多的多
Robert Zane is paying you to testify.
你女儿仍能拿到
It's on top of whatever settlement
之前协议的要求
your daughter is still gonna get.
你只需要三缄其口
All you have to do is keep your mouth shut.
你的钱对我没有吸引力了
Yeah, I'm not interested in your money.
不  加洛  你不懂  这...
No, Gallo, you're not getting me, this--
是你不懂
You're not getting me.
我根本不在乎你的钱
I don't give a God damn about your money.
罗伯特・赞恩告诉我了
Robert Zane already told me
你还会回来想办法害我
you'd be in here trying to screw me over.
我没想害你
I'm not trying to screw you over.
那你上个月为什么一直在要我做
Then why have you been trying to get me to do
-和现在要求相反的事  -因为
- the exact opposite thing for the last month? - Because--
因为你们俩只在乎
Because the two of you don't give a shit
各自利益
about anything but yourselves.
情况有变
The situation has changed.
你知道什么没变吗
You know what hasn't changed?
丹妮斯
Denise.
她对我的看法
What she thinks of me.
-弗兰克  这  -你看  你之前来这
- Frank, that's-- - See, you came in here
想让我把她的爱买回来
trying to get me to buy her love back.
我差点就做了
I almost did it.
但是光用钱我从她那什么也得不到
But I can't get anything from her with just money.
我得让她看我站在证人席
I need her to see me get up on that stand
承认我犯的错并且请求原谅
admit what I did and ask for forgiveness.
罗伯特・赞恩理解我  因为他也有女儿
Robert Zane understands that because he's got a daughter.
-我能理解  -不  你不能
- I understand that-- - No, you don't.
我得让她看见我的行动
I need her to see me do this.
你和哈维说什么也不能改变我的心意
And nothing you or Harvey can say is gonna change that.
然后你说
And then you said,
"是笨蛋先生  非常感谢"
"It's Mr. Dipshit, thank you very much."
如果他在
Well, if he's gonna be a stickler
预订姓名问题上继续纠缠...
about what name is on the reservation...
那一周剩下的时间
And then for the rest of the weekend,
我们一杯酒钱都没付过
we didn't have to pay for a single drink.
这是件好事  鉴于你给饭店所有人
Which was a good thing because you ordered tequila shots
-都点了龙舌兰酒  -当时是五月五日节
- for everyone in the restaurant. - It was Cinco de Mayo.
为庆祝墨西哥军队击败法国殖民军而设立
当时是八月九日
It was August 9th.
我没想到你还记得
I can't believe you still remember that.
那段时间的很多事我都记得
I remember a lot of things about those days.
所以我都不敢相信
Which is why I can't believe that there's not a, uh,
你至今都没结婚
a Mr. Donna Paulson yet.
你知道我有自己的标准
Well. You know I have my standards.
我很高兴你没有放低要求
Well, I'm glad to see you haven't lowered them.
实话告诉你  我要求还变高了
To tell you the truth, I actually raised them.
至少是在工作方面
At least professionally.
你是说你终于不给哈维打工了吗
You mean you finally stopped working for Harvey?
是也不是
Yes and no.
我还在律所工作  但现在是首席运营官
I still work at the firm, but I'm COO now.
-唐娜  这太棒了  -确实是
- Donna, that is fantastic. - It is.
那你呢
So what about you?
还没结婚吗
No Mrs. Meadows yet?
事实上  我...
Um, actually, I--
我三年前就结婚了
I got married about three years ago.
马克  如果你已婚
Mark, if you're married,
为什么要同意和我出来吃饭
why did you agree to have lunch with me?
因为你打电话来邀请我
Because you called and you invited me
而且  我以为只是顿午饭而已...
and--and I thought it's just lunch, and--
你心里清楚这不是普通的午餐会面
This hasn't felt like just lunch and you know it.
的确不是
No, it hasn't.
老实告诉你
To tell you the truth,
我一直都在想你
I think about you all the time.
我妻子和我已经
And my wife and I have been
吵了几个月的架了
at each other's throats for months.
然后你电话就来了  我想着见见你
And then you called and I thought that I would meet you
看看会发生什么
and just see what happened.
我可以告诉你不会发生什么
Well, I can tell you what's not gonna happen.
你的婚姻问题不能通过我来解决
I'm not gonna be the answer to your problems.
我很抱歉
Well, I'm--I'm so sorry.
听着  我不会谎称
Look, I'm not gonna lie
我从来没想过你
and say that I don't think about you, too, from time to time.
我想过
I do.
但是我们俩不能以这种方式重新开始
But this can't be the way that things start up again with us.
所以如果某个时刻  你打电话告诉我
So if at some point, you call and you say
你和你妻子已经结束了
that things are over between you and your wife
你想和我在一起
and you wanna go out with me,
这个我可以接受
I'd be open to that.
但是现在不行
But I'm not open to this.
我理解
I understand.
很高兴见到你  马克
It was good to see you, Mark.
我也是  唐娜
It's good to see you too, Donna.
瑞秋
Rachel.
你好
Hey.
-见到你真高兴  -是吗
- You are a sight for sore eyes. - Am I?
怎么了
Whoa, what's going on?
今天不顺吗
Did you have a bad day?
我本来挺好的直到我发现
I was actually having a great day until I found out
谋杀案的证人是弗兰克・加洛
that the witness in the murder case is Frank Gallo.
-瑞秋  我准备  -告诉我吗
- Rachel, I was gonna-- - Gonna tell me?
什么时候  等事情结束以后吗
When, exactly? When the whole thing was over?
因为我还发现你和哈维
Because I also found out that you and Harvey
去找我爸把这个案子接下来了
went to my dad to keep this thing alive.
-瑞秋  -我告诉你
- Rachel-- - How many times
多少次了  我能照顾好我自己
do I have to tell you I can take care of myself?
你想让我说什么
What did you want me to say?
我不应该去找加洛
That I shouldn't have gone to Gallo?
还是我当初就不该
Or that I shouldn't have taken this whole thing on
接下这个案子
in the first place?
因为我不会这么说的
Because I am never gonna say that.
跟这些没关系
This has nothing to do with any of that.
而是你对我作为律师的尊重
This has to do with you respecting me as a lawyer.
所以你是说如果我把计划告诉你
So you're telling me that if I had let you in on the plan,
你觉得就没有问题了
you would've been good with all of it.
我是不知道我会不会同意你的这些做法
I don't know if I would've been good with any of it.
我知道的是你得明白
What I do know is that you need to get through your head
我是个成年女性
that I am a grown woman
不是什么被困少女
and that I am not a damsel in distress
需要保护
that needs protecting.
无论是什么事  唐娜  我现在都没法考虑
Whatever it is, Donna, I don't have it in me.
没事  路易  我都不知道你在这
It's okay, Louis. I didn't even know you were up here.
如果你想一个人待着  我可以...
If you wanna be alone, I can
希拉要结婚了
Sheila's getting married.
我很遗憾
I'm so sorry.
她不想告诉我因为她觉得
She didn't wanna tell me because she thought
我接受不了
I couldn't handle it.
我明白
I get it.
也许
Maybe.
但是你不知道的是
But what you don't get is what it's like
在一年内发现两次
to find out twice in one year
你觉得是你一生所爱的人并不想要你
that the person you thought was the love of your life
是什么样的感觉
doesn't want you.
我比你想的更明白这种感受
I understand that more than you think.
什么意思
What do you mean?
我今天和我的一个前男友一起吃了午饭
I had lunch with an ex-boyfriend today.
一个我特别在意的人
Someone I cared a lot about.
我找了他  想知道是否还有可能
I looked him up, wondering if there was still something there
当我们吃饭的时候  他告诉我他结婚了
and while we were eating, he told me he was married.
那他为什么要和你一起吃饭
Why'd he have lunch with you?
因为  路易
Because, Louis.
人们比你所想的要更复杂
People are more complicated than you think.
对于希拉来说并不复杂
Well, it's not complicated for Sheila.
她找到了她的真命天子  就那样
She's found her man, and that is that.
路易  我不确定我放心
Louis, I'm not sure I feel comfortable leaving you
留你一个人在这里
up here all alone.
没事的  唐娜  我不会跳下去的
It's okay, Donna. I'm not gonna jump.
除非你能保证我会落在希拉的未婚夫身上
Unless you can guarantee me I can land on Sheila's fiancé.
好  你会没事的
Okay. You're gonna be all right.
但是我还是不打算留你一个人在这
But I'm still not leaving you up here all alone.
无论你想说什么  我都不想听
Whatever it is, I don't need to hear it
因为我已经知道你要说什么了
because I already know what you're gonna say.
不管怎样我都要说
Well, I'm gonna say it anyway.
我把案子给你不是让你去打官司的
I didn't bring you this case to take you to court.
我给你这个案子是为了让你为这些人伸张正义
I brought it to you so you could give these people justice.
扯淡  你把这个案子给我
Bullshit. You brought it to me
是为了解决你自己的问题
to get you out of hot water.
正如我告诉你的
And like I already told you,
这是我的案子
this is my case.
你没权利告诉我怎么处理
Don't you dare tell me how to run it.
我知道  罗伯特  但是
I know that Robert, but look,
如果你挖得太深
if you dig too deep,
我的人会因为他
it's gonna end up putting one of my own
没犯过的罪而坐牢
behind bars for a crime he didn't commit.
用脚趾头想都知道你说的是谁
Well, it doesn't take too much for me to guess who that is.
我一点也不在乎亚历克斯・威廉姆斯
And I don't give a shit about Alex Williams.
你知道我在乎什么吗
You know what I do give a shit about?
美国有全世界百分之五的人口
The United States is 5% of the world's population.
但却有全世界四分之一的囚犯
But it's got 25% of its prisoners.
但那不是你们这些白人所在乎的
But that's not something you white guys want to talk about.
-罗伯特  -我在哈莱姆
- Robert-- - I grew up
最恶劣的地方长大
in the roughest part of Harlem there is.
我街区的孩子  十之八九
Nine out of ten kids on my block
蹲了监狱
ended up in places like that.
我活着的每一天
And every day of my life,
都在想
I think...
他们只能自求多福
there but by the grace of God.
他们把这些孩子
And they're taking these kids--
像我认识的那些孩子一样  他们
like the ones I knew- and they're
延长他们的刑期  还杀掉了几个
extending their sentences and murdering some of them.
所以无论你要说些什么  做些什么
So no matter what you do or what you say,
他们都会接受我的提议  上庭讨个公道的
they're going to take my offer or we're going to trial.
不管怎样  他们都会付出代价
Either way, they're gonna pay.
哈维  我正想要打给你
Harvey. I was just about to call you.
既然你还没打
Since you didn't already,
我想你没搞定加洛
I'm guessing you couldn't convince Gallo
不去作证
not to testify.
他不要钱  哈维
He doesn't want our money, Harvey.
他想要他女儿原谅他
He wants his daughter's forgiveness
他觉得让他女儿原谅他的唯一方式就是去作证
and thinks the only way he's gonna get it is by testifying.
扯淡  他有所求
Bullshit. He wants something.
我们只需要弄清楚他想要什么
We just need to find out what it is.
听我说  我和他面对面谈了
Listen to me. I was in the room with him.
他想要得到他女儿的原谅是真的
This thing with his daughter is real.
-他不会退缩的  -该死
- He's not gonna back down. - Son of a bitch.
-我们现在做什么  -没办法的办法
- What are we gonna do now? - I hate to say it.
我们可能得找找赞恩的把柄
We may need to find some dirt on Zane.
哈维  我是不会因为一件起初由我们
Harvey, I'm not gonna blackmail my future father-in-law
给他的案子敲诈我未来的岳父的
about a case that we gave him to begin with.
不是你给他的  是我给的
You didn't give it to him. I did.
我这么做是为了确保两件事
And I did it to make sure two things happened,
其中一件就是救亚历克斯・威廉姆斯
and one was saving Alex Williams.
所以如果你不愿意去找赞恩的把柄
So if you don't wanna find something on Zane,
我去找
I will.
你们俩都不用去找
Neither one of you has to.
-瑞秋  -哈维  我懂这些事情
- Rachel-- - Harvey, I know how things work.
我是说  你不用去找
I meant, you don't have to find
我爸的把柄  因为我知道
dirt on my father because I know
怎么阻止弗兰克・加洛作证
how to stop Frank Gallo from testifying.
但我爸不会是唯一一个不喜欢这做法的人
But my dad isn't gonna be the only one who doesn't like it.
你俩也不会喜欢的
You two aren't gonna like it either.
-为什么  -因为这涉及到
- Why not? - Because it involves
通过我
impugning his integrity
质疑他的人品
and doing it through me.
如果你说的和我理解的一样
If you're saying what I think you're saying,
那是在玩火
that's playing with fire.
我说过我不介意玩火
And I already told you I don't have a problem playing with fire.
我介意的是被排除在外
My problem is being left out of the game.
所以如果我爸有问题
So if my dad has an issue with it,
让他来找我
you tell him to take it up with me.
路易  那个哥伦比亚大学的女人
Louis, that woman from Columbia University's
又打来了
on the line again.
她想知道你怎么看她的学生
She'd like to know what you thought about her candidate.
告诉她我们已经雇了人了
Tell her we already filled the position.
路易  告诉我怎么了
Louis, tell me what's going on.
你费了那么大的劲让他们参与进来
You went all the way over there to get them on board
现在你却让我和那个女人说谎
and now you're asking me to lie to this woman.
事实是我不想看到她
What's going on is I don't wanna see her,
我不想和她说话  我不想听到她的名字
I don't wanna talk to her, I don't wanna hear her name.
所以如果你不想说谎的话  那就别说
So if you don't wanna lie, then don't.
但是我是不会接那个电话的
But I am not taking that call.
迈克  瑞秋的计划是可行的
Look, Mike, Rachel's plan could work,
但是肯定会气坏赞恩的  你知道的
but it's gonna piss Zane off and you know it.
更不用说对加洛的影响
Not to mention what it's gonna do to Gallo.
相信我  瑞秋和我可以解决好这次的争执的
Rachel and I can take care of the fallout, trust me.
在你昨天晚上来之前
Before you got there last night,
她明确说她能照顾好自己
she made it clear that she can handle herself.
我不在乎她认为自己能照顾谁
Yeah, I don't care what she thinks she can handle.
-我不会这样做  -那你的计划是什么
- I'm not doing it. - Then what exactly is your plan,
听证会五分钟后就开始
because the hearing's in five minutes
我们没有其它办法阻止加洛作证
and we don't have another way to stop Gallo from testifying.
你来这里干嘛  布莱顿
What the hell are you doing here, Bratton?
我来确定你在做自己的工作
I'm to make sure you're doing your job.
鬼扯  我又不为你工作
Bullshit, I don't work for you.
我没说过你为我工作  但如果你不能
I didn't say you did. But if you can't
解决此事  你也就不能
make this thing go away, you're not gonna be working
为改造公司工作了  马斯特森建筑公司也一样
for Reform Corp. Or Masterson Construction either.
-是吗  -当然
- Is that a fact? - Sure as hell is.
你不阻止我们的监狱友人作证
You don't stop our prison friend from testifying,
我就会接手此事
I'm gonna take this thing over
而我要做的第一件事是
and the first thing I'm going to do
交出一个替罪羊
is offer up a sacrificial lamb
名叫亚历克斯・威廉姆斯
named Alex Williams.
你现在觉得瑞秋的计划怎么样
How do you feel about Rachel's plan now?
各位  这是第二次
Gentlemen, this is the second time
在本案中提及弗兰克・加洛的问题
the issue of Frank Gallo's come up in this case.
-这次又是怎么回事  -法官
- What is it this time? - What it is, Your Honor,
这次是因为斯佩克特知道加洛会
is Mr. Specter knows Mr. Gallo is gonna
整得他跪地求饶
take him out at the knees
所以他会不顾一切阻止加洛这么做
and he's gonna do anything he can to stop him.
我不顾一切是因为弗兰克・加洛
I'll do anything I can because Frank Gallo
将要做伪证  而罗伯特・赞恩也心里有数
is about to commit perjury and Robert Zane knows it.
你在公开法庭指控他人有此罪状
You accuse someone of something like that
最好是他妈的拿点证据出来
in an open court, you better damn well have proof.
赞恩先生  注意言辞
Mr. Zane, watch yourself.
还有斯佩克特先生  他说得没错
And Mr. Specter, he's right.
我知道  法官
I know that, Your Honor.
所以我带了证据来
Which is why I have proof right here.
那是什么
And what is that?
弗兰克・加洛发送的瑞秋・赞恩的照片
Pictures of Rachel Zane sent by Frank Gallo
设计胁迫她父亲教唆其作伪证
designed to intimidate her father into suborning perjury.
你在撒谎
That is a lie!
不管信封里是什么东西  全是鬼扯
Whatever's in that envelope is bullshit.
赞恩先生  我不会追究你这番话
Mr. Zane, I'm going to let that language go
也不会指控你任何罪证
and I don't want to accuse you of anything,
但这些照片确实表明一个罪犯
but these photos do indicate that a known criminal
在威胁你的女儿
is threatening your daughter.
我才不在乎它们表明了什么
I don't give a shit what they indicate.
我从未见过这些照片
I've never seen them before in my life
我也不会教唆伪证
and I don't suborn perjury.
好了  我不知道是怎么回事
That's enough. I don't know what's going on here,
但直到我把事情搞清楚之前
but until I get to the bottom of this,
弗兰克・加洛不能作证
Frank Gallo is not testifying.
混蛋  你利用我女儿跟我作对
You son of a bitch. You used my daughter against me.
我一定会击败你
I'm gonna God damn knock you out.
罗伯特  不是你先对付我的吗
Robert, don't you come at me.
你不希望我对付你是因为你知道
You don't want me coming at you because you know
我一旦对你下手  你就完蛋了
once I got my hands on you you're done!
所以我要先打败你
Which is why I'll drop you before you do.
-尽管来打败我啊  -罗伯特
- Go ahead and drop me! - Robert.
你不会动手的  因为你知道这样不对
You're not gonna throw a punch because you know you're wrong.
罗伯特  罗伯特  住手
Robert, Robert! Hey, Robert, Robert! Stop!
这是瑞秋的主意
It was Rachel's idea.
-你刚才说什么  -哈维甚至不想这么做
- What did you just say? - Harvey didn't even wanna do it.
鬼扯  这是她的主意
Bullshit, it was her idea.
哈维  她是个成年人  作出了自己的决定
Robert, she's a grown woman, she made a decision.
你不相信我的话  可以亲自去问她
You don't believe me, you can ask her yourself.
但我告诉你  你只是想发火
But I'm telling you, you wanna be angry at someone,
-但别拿哈维当出气筒  -我不在乎
- do not take it out on Harvey. - I don't care
这是谁的主意
whose idea it was.
你利用她来诋毁我
You used her to slander me!
在公开法庭上
In open court!
你该为自己感到羞耻
You should be ashamed of yourself.
还有你  告诉你的改造公司同伙们
And you--you tell your Reform Corp Buddies
弗兰克・加洛无论如何一定会作证
that Frank Gallo is gonna take that stand one way or another.
他们做什么也阻止不了
And there's nothing they can do to stop it.
-马克  你好  -你好
- Mark, hi. - Hey, um,
希望我没有打扰你
I hope I'm not interrupting.
没有  其实我在...
No, actually, I'm just, um--
今晚的工作已经结束了
I'm just finishing up for the night.
你还在吗
Are you still there?
对
Yeah, um--
抱歉  我只是...
Sorry, um, I'm just--
-马克  -等等  拜托  唐娜
- Mark. - Hold on, please, Donna.
让我...就让我把话说出来
Let me just-- let me just get this out.
那天见到你让我找回很多感觉
Seeing you the other day brought up a lot of feelings.
我也是  但你结婚了
It did for me, too. But you're married.
-不太幸福  -马克
- Not happily. - Mark--
事实上  我曾经离开过你
The thing is, I walked away from you once before.
从那以后...
And ever since...
我一直在想如果我没有离开你  会怎么样
I--I wonder what would've happened if I hadn't--
我只是...我不能再一次离你而去
I just--I can't walk away from you again.
你想说什么
What are you saying?
我的工作室本周要举办一个会议
My office is hosting a conference this week
每个人都会留在城里  所以...
and everyone's staying in the city, so...
我在周六前都不会返回康涅狄格州
I'm not going back to Connecticut until Saturday.
我想在回去前见见你
I'd like to see you before I do.
我该说些什么
What am I supposed to say to that?
你什么都不必说
You don't have to say anything.
但我只是想让你知道
But I just wanted you to know
我未来两天都会住在嘉丽酒店
that I'll be staying at the Carlyle for the next two nights.
508房间
Room 508.
你妻子怎么办
What about your wife?
我不知道我该怎么处理
I don't know how I'm gonna handle that.
我也肯定没法明天就把这事解决掉
And I definitely won't be able to handle it by tomorrow.
所以如果你不想见我  我完全理解
So if you don't wanna see me, I'll understand.
但我得打这个电话
But I had to call.
晚安  唐娜
Good night, Donna.
晚安  马克
Good night, Mark.
格蕾琴  我说了我不接任何电话
Gretchen, I told you I'm not taking any calls.
路易吗
Louis?
希拉  你打了我的专用线
Sheila. You called my private line.
时机不对吗
Is this a bad time?
我不会说时机很好
I wouldn't say it's a great time.
路易  我说我没有告诉你我去哥伦比亚的事
Louis, I lied when I said I didn't tell you
是因为不想伤害你  那是谎话
about being at Columbia because I didn't wanna hurt you.
那你为什么不告诉我
Well, then why didn't you tell me?
因为我还没有忘记你
Because I haven't gotten you out of my system.
当我说这句话
And when I say that,
我真正的意思是  路易
what I'm really saying is, Louis,
在我结婚之前  我想最后要你一次
I want your body one last time before I walk down that aisle.
这是什么意思
Say what, now?
我想吞噬你每一寸肌肤
I wanna devour every inch of your flesh.
我要让你用六种方式震撼我的世界
I want you to rock my world six ways from Sunday.
-我要你...  -我想我理解了...
- I want to-- - I think I get the--
不许打断我
Do not interrupt me!
我要你在惊天动地的12到36小时内
Because I demand a travel to the moon and back
带我冲上月球再返回地面
seven to nine more times
我要七次  九次  更多次
in one life-shattering 12-36 hour period.
-天哪  -然后我要让你
- Oh, my God. - That's when I plan on
尖叫到声嘶力竭
making you scream until you can't scream anymore.
希拉  你突然是怎么了
Sheila, where is this coming from?
你知道是怎么了
You know exactly where it's coming from.
从你像维京战神一样踏入我的
It started the second you strutted into my office
办公室
like a Viking god,
准备劫掠一个无助的小女人开始
ready to pillage a helpless maiden.
我只是来电话问问申请的事
I was just coming in to check on the candidates.
我都不知道你...
I didn't even know that you were--
这就更性感了
That's what makes it so hot.
希拉  虽然你的描述
Shirley, even though this image
已经让我欲火焚身
is making my Viking mast unfurl to full sail,
但我觉得这样好像不太好
I don't think what you're suggesting is a good idea.
那是因为我还没告诉你
Well, that's because I haven't told you
我打算同意让你做你一直以来
that I'm finally gonna let you do that thing
渴望已久的事
that you always wanted to do.
-包括...  -是的
- Even the-- - Yes.
-还有...  -是的
- And with the-- - Yes.
那口音呢
And what about the accent?
随便加  路易
Oh, with all the accents, Louis.
随便加
With all the accents.
-口齿不清呢  -不行
- What about the lisp? - No.
希拉  我不能这样
Ahh! Sheila, I can't!
我尊重你的正直  路易
I respect your integrity, Louis.
但这不足以阻止我
But not enough to stop me from waiting
今晚在我们的老房间等你
for you tomorrow night in our old hotel suite.
战斗室吗
The War Room?
一点没错
The very one.
路易  你得来一下大办公室
Louis, you've gotta come down to the bullpen for a second.
你绝不会相信布莱恩给朗斯顿和解
You're not gonna believe what Brian cooked up
想出了什么好办法
for the Langston settlement.
-现在不行  瑞去  -为什么
- I can't right now, Rachel. - Why not?
只要一下下
It's only going to take a second.
因为我现在不打算离开桌子  瑞秋
Because I'm not getting up right now, Rachel,
说什么都不行
and there's nothing you can say to change that.
路易  你怎么了
Louis, what's going on?
刚和希拉通完电话
Just got off the phone with Sheila.
她要结婚了  她想和我在她结婚前
She's getting married and she wants to have one last fling
最后放纵一次
before she goes down the aisle.
你不想这么做
And you don't wanna do that because
因为你不想成为这种人
you don't wanna be that kind of person.
-是的  -那还有什么问题
- No, I don't. - So then what's the problem?
问题是...
The problem is--is...
我的生活好久以来都很不顺
I haven't had anything go my way in so long,
我都不知道顺心是什么感觉了
I can't even remember what that's like.
我真的很想有一晚上
And I could really use a night where
让我忘掉所有痛苦  忘掉自己
I can forget my pain and feel good about myself.
路易  我不知道改怎么建议
Louis, I can't tell you what the answer is
因为做这种事
because it's not a small thing
不是件小事
to do something like that.
但我想说  我觉得你很善良
But if it helps, I know you have a good heart.
所以不管你怎么决定  都不会改变
So whatever you decide, it's not gonna change
我对你的看法
how I feel about you.
谢谢  瑞秋
Thanks, Rachel.
你来干什么  律师
What are you doing here, Counselor?
我来是因为我有关于改造公司的
I'm here because I have relevant information
-信息告诉你  -如果是这样
- on the Reform Corp. Matter. - And if that's the case,
那你应该和罗伯特・赞恩
you should be doing it in chambers
-一起在法官办公室  -法官大人
- and Robert Zane should be there. - Your Honor,
罗伯特・赞恩疯了
Robert Zane's not in his right mind.
你看到他昨天的反应了
You saw what happened to him yesterday
所以在你对弗兰克・加洛的事宣判前
and that's why before you rule on Frank Gallo--
-别说了  斯佩克特先生  -不行
- Stop right there, Mr. Specter. - No, I'm not gonna stop there.
-别说了  -法官大人....
- Yes, you are. - Your Honor--
弗兰克・加洛死了
Frank Gallo is dead.
-什么  -他昨晚在囚室被谋杀了
- What? - He was murdered in his cell last night.
所以不管你要说什么更他有关的
So whatever it was that you were going
都与本案无关了
to say about him is irrelevant.
那人不能出庭了
The man can't testify.
所以我想可以让他安息了
So I think it's time to let him rest in peace.
唐娜
Donna.
你站这里多久了
How long have you been standing there?
我刚路过  没认出来你
I was just walking by and I didn't recognize you.
所以你在想  那个站在哈维办公室的
And you thought, who is that strange woman
陌生女人是谁
in Harvey's office?
我不是这么想的
That's not what I thought.
你见到哈维了吗
Have you seen Harvey, by any chance?
他今天都不在
He's actually out for the rest of the day.
没事  晚上见他好了
That's okay. I'll just see him tonight.
我知道了
Oh, I get it.
你不告而来
You stopped by to surprise him
是因为这是你们两个月纪念日
because it's your two month anniversary.
-你怎么知道的  -我很关心他
- How can you know that? - Because I care about him.
你进入他的生活
And you coming into his life...
是个值得纪念的日子
is a memorable event.
很高兴见到你  唐娜
Well, it was good to see you, Donna.
卡尔博纳
Carbone.
什么
I'm sorry.
那地方很简陋
It's a hole in the wall,
但却是哈维最喜欢的餐馆之一
but it's one of Harvey's favorite places.
如果你要订餐
So if you're looking for a reservation--
其实  我已经订过了
Actually, I already have one.
我猜猜
Oh, let me guess.
-就在卡尔博纳  -是的
- At Carbone. - Yes.
你们肯定会有个愉快的夜晚
Well, I'm sure you'll have a great time.
谢谢你的建议  唐娜
Thank you for the recommendation, Donna.
你在这儿  我到处找你
There you are. I've been looking all over for you.
-怎么了  瑞秋  -我在想
- What is it, Rachel? - Okay, I was thinking,
我们不是说好要一起喝酒但一直没去
we never got to have those drinks we talked about
唐娜  我知道你最近
and, Donna, I know you've been going through
事情很多
a lot of stuff, lately.
所以我在想也许你可以
So I thought maybe you could use a night
把烦恼都抛诸脑后一夜
where you just lose your troubles
让自己放纵一下
and just feel good about yourself.
-确实  -怎么样
- I could. - So, what do you say?
那今晚哈利艾特・斯佩克特
Is Harriett Specter available
能和米歇尔・罗斯出去喝一杯吗
to go out with Michelle Ross tonight?
今晚不行  瑞秋  我有约了
I can't tonight, Rachel; I have plans.
好神秘  是约了个帅哥吗
What's mysterious. What do you have, a hot date?
算是吧
Yeah. Something like that.
-他在吗  -在  但你不能进去
- Is he in? - Yes, but you can't go in there.
你拦我试试
Try and stop me.
-等等  -你个混蛋
- Wait a second. - You son of a bitch.
你杀了弗兰克・加洛
You murdered Frank Gallo.
阿什莉  我来处理吧
Ashley, I'll handle this.
我不知道你在说什么
I have no idea what you're talking about.
放屁  你说过如果我不能阻止他作证
Bullshit! You said if I couldn't stop him from testifying,
你就会找其他人来阻止他
you'd find someone who could.
我是说会找托马斯・布莱顿
I meant I'd get Thomas Bratton involved.
不是说杀人灭口
I didn't mean I'd kill a man.
而你也确实阻止加洛出庭作证了
And you did stop Gallo from testifying,
又有什么关系呢
so why would it matter?
因为他想确认罗伯特・赞恩
Because he wanted to make sure that Robert Zane
没有改变法庭决定  你就杀了他
didn't reverse it, so you had him murdered.
那你说说我是怎么策划的这起故意谋杀
And how exactly did I arrange this supposed murder?
就跟你杀了那个警卫然后掩盖罪行一样
The same damn way you killed that guard and covered it up.
我再说一遍  哈维  听不懂你说什么
Once again, Harvey, I have no idea what you're talking about.
随便你想怎么指责我
And you can accuse me of anything you want,
那个人可是冷酷无情的罪犯
but that man was a hardened criminal
很多人有很多理由想要他死
who could've been killed by anyone for anything.
我才不会因为这个费半点心思
And I am not gonna lose a second of sleep over it.
恕我不赞同
I beg to differ.
-罗伯特  -什么情况
- Robert. - What the hell is going on here?
我告诉你什么情况
I'll tell you what's going on.
有点东西要给你看
I got something for you to see.
可不是什么网飞剧上演的
And it's not on Netflix.
弗兰克・加洛  09842号囚犯
Frank Gallo, prisoner 09842.
丹伯里联邦监狱
Danbury Federal Prison.
好了  废话不多说
All right. Enough bullshit.
我是你的律师  这些都将不被采信
I'm your lawyer. None of this is admissible.
现在  告诉我真相
Now tell me the truth,
好让我了解什么情况
so I know what I'm dealing with.
你想要真相  那我就告诉你真相
All right, you want the truth, let's just get to it.
一个警卫给了某个外面的律师一张纸条
There was a guard, sent a letter to some lawyer on the outside
那个律师对监狱的事情起了疑心
who was getting suspicious of what was going on in there.
他们想让我警告他
They wanted me to remind him
他到底几斤几两
of where he was in the food chain.
-你乐意去做吗  -不  我不想
- And you were happy to do it. - No, I wasn't.
在这里我们可能是硬汉
We were hard men in there.
是暴徒  是杀人犯
Tough guys, murderers.
那警卫只是个善良的老头
That guard was just a sweet, old man.
一辈子都未曾与人不善
Never hurt a soul in all his years.
你觉得我会信吗
And you expect me to believe all that.
信不信由你  我只是说出真相
You can believe it or not, it's the truth.
我跟他们说我不做
So I told them I wouldn't do it
直到他们的老大
until whoever was running the show
直接找到了我
came to me directly.
是他们叫来的
And they made that happen.
他们没办法
They had no choice.
第二天  那人就出现在我牢房前
Next day, the guy showed up right in my God damn cell
就跟这座监狱是他建的似的
like he owned the place,
而事实也确实如此  -那人是谁
which he did. - And who exactly was that?
罗杰・夏皮罗  改造公司的首席执行官
Roger Shapiro. CEO of Reform Corp.
然后发生了什么
And then what happened?
我
I, uh--
那天晚上我在食堂截住他
I got him alone that night in the mess hall.
你都想不到  那老头还挺能打
Wouldn't you know, the old man still had some fight in him.
然后我意识到  不是他死就是我死
Next thing I knew, it was him or me, so--
所以我把他放倒了
I had to put him down.
你杀了他
You killed him.
是的
Yeah.
我杀了他
I killed him.
之后你怎么做的
And then what did you do?
我告诉他们这次之后  我就洗手不干了
I told them I was done, out, no more.
第二天晚上  罗杰・夏皮罗
Next night, Roger Shapiro sent five of my friends
让我的五个朋友也对我做了同样的事
to do the same thing to me.
看来你麻烦不小啊  罗杰
Looks like you're in some deep shit, Roger.
我不信
I don't believe it.
所以你俩是合起伙来整我是吗
So you two were in on this together.
用你的话说  我不知道你在说什么
To quote you, I have no idea what you're talking about.
我今天早上绝对没有去罗伯特家里
I certainly didn't go to Robert's house this morning
告诉他我觉得你杀了弗兰克・加洛
and tell him that I think that you had Frank Gallo murdered
因此他不能出庭作证了
so he wouldn't be able to testify.
我也绝对没有说如果你真的杀了他
And I certainly didn't say if you had,
那你就犯了个大错  因为现在这段录像
you made a huge mistake because now this tape
就成了临终忏悔
is a death bed confession
法律上是可采信的
and by law is admissible.
我之前说的那些
And all that bullshit I came up with,
关于罗伯特被弗兰克・加洛恐吓
about Robert being intimidated by Frank Gallo,
就根本不成立了
well, that doesn't apply anymore
因为弗兰克・加洛已经死了
because Frank Gallo's dead.
-你们到底想怎样  -我想要的
- So what do you want? - What I want
就是你因谋杀罪入狱
is for you to go away for murder.
但那是不可能的
But that's not gonna happen,
所以我会给你一个我满意的数字
so I'll settle for the number I wanted in the first place.
而你从此以后再不能对犯人做这种烂事
But you're never gonna pull this shit again on prisoners
如果你这么做了
because if you do,
我才不管什么亚历克斯・威廉姆斯
I don't care about Alex Williams.
这段录像就会交到司法部
This tape goes to the Department of Justice
而你  就会被关进你自己建的监狱
and you are headed to one of your own prisons,
不出五秒
five seconds later.
我想这个选择我能接受
I think that's something that I could work with.
如果没有其他事  还请你们出去
Now, if there's nothing else, I'd like you both to leave.
咱们还没完
Oh, we're not done with you yet.
-还有什么  -我来告诉你
- What now? - I'll tell you what now,
你要写一些东西给我
you're gonna write up something for me
而你不会喜欢的
and you're not gonna like it.
但如果你不想蹲大牢
But if you wanna stay out of prison,
你就得保证  你所写的都按我的要求来
you're gonna make damn sure it says exactly what I need it to.
什么情况
What the hell is this?
汤米
Tommy.
你能告诉我你怎么进来的吗
You mind telling me how the hell you got in here?
这里的人们都喜欢我  汤米
People like me here, Tommy.
所以我进来了
That's how I got in.
你应该问我为什么来这
But the question you should be asking is why I'm here.
我才不管你过来干嘛
I don't give a shit why you're here.
我要拿回我的宣誓书
I want my God damn affidavit back.
当然了  你还想让我签
Sure thing. You also want me to sign over
我自己住的汉普顿斯别墅的契约呢
the deed to my house in the Hamptons, while I'm at it?
那破房子你自己留着住吧
You can keep your shitty house.
毕竟你辞职后还得有个遮风挡雨的地儿
Because you're gonna need someplace to go after you resign.
你说什么
What did you just say to me?
他说他过来要他的宣誓书
He said he's here for his affidavit
还有你的辞呈  你个自以为是的老混球
and your resignation, you smug piece of shit.
你们这是  准备让我滚蛋吗
What you guys, plan on beating it out of me?
你们才是该滚蛋的人
Because that's the only way you'd get it.
我们不会为难老年人  汤米
We don't need to beat up an old man, Tommy.
只想让你看看这个
We just need to show you this.
那是什么
What's that?
这是罗杰・夏皮罗的签字认罪书
That's a signed confession from Roger Shapiro,
上面写着他参与了阴谋
say he entered into a conspiracy
与马斯特森建筑公司合谋
with Masterson Construction to defraud
欺骗了联邦政府
the United States government.
而这阴谋就是你一手策划的
And that that conspiracy was arranged by you.
不可能  罗杰不可能这么做
No way. Roger would never do that.
但他做了  出于和他同样的原因
Oh, he did it. For the same reason
你也会按我们说的做
you're gonna give us what we want.
因为我们抓住了他的要害
We had him by the balls.
就像我现在抓住了你的要害一样  汤米
Just like I got you right now, Tommy.
你可以给他打个电话问问
So you can pick up the phone and call him,
或者看看我的表情像不像在说谎
or you can look at my face and see I'm not lying.
不管怎样  没拿到我们想要的结果
But either way, we're not leaving here
我们都不会离开
without getting what we want.
你们也不能
I'm not going to stand here
站这儿等我写辞职信吧
and write my resignation letter in front of you two, okay?
好在我们帮你写好了
Then it's a good thing we wrote one up for you.
对了  记得我说你说你欠我人情对吧
By the way, remember when I told you you owed me?
我想现在我们扯平了
I'd pretty much say we're even.
我觉得这相当不相当
I don't think this word even means what you think it means.
是吗
Oh, well, is that a fact?
当然了  我只是拒绝你一个工作
You're damn right it is. I turned down a job offer.
你可是被我救出了监狱
You were gonna go to prison.
你这辈子都欠我的
You owe me for the rest of your life.
收到  你和我  扯平了
Got it. Me and you, square.
我再说一次  你对扯平的理解
Once again, I don't think the word square
-也偏差很大  -没错
- means what you think it means. - You're right.
再讹你一顿饭才够
We still gotta go eat on you.
抱歉  今晚不行  亚历克斯  我有约
Sorry, can't tonight, Alex. I got other plans.
你怎么来了
What are you doing here?
我来道歉
I came to apologize for what I did.
你不是说是瑞秋的主意吗
I thought you said it was Rachel's idea.
没错  但你也说我该阻止她
It was, but you said i should've stopped it in its tracks
你是对的
and you were right.
罗伯特  我很抱歉
Robert, I'm sorry.
我爱瑞秋  我绝不会伤害她
I love Rachel. I would never do anything to hurt her.
但我也不该伤害你
But I should've known to never do anything to hurt you.
能说出这种话也很需要勇气  迈克
It takes a big man to say that, Mike.
谢谢
I appreciate it.
而且我也不得不承认  最后的结果
And I'd be lying if I didn't admit it worked out
对大家都好
for everybody in the end.
也不是所有人
Yeah, not everybody.
对那个混蛋的遭遇我可毫不愧疚
I'm not losing any sleep over that son of a bitch.
他也许没拿瑞秋威胁我
He may not have threatened Rachel to me,
但绝对是拿瑞秋威胁你了
but he sure as hell threatened her to you.
我知道  我也知道他是杀人犯
I know. And I know he was a murderer.
但哈维给我看了录像
But Harvey showed me that tape.
你能看出他有多爱女儿
You can see how much he cared about his daughter.
而事实是
Fact of the matter is,
他们再也无法相见了
they're never gonna see each other again.
敬弗兰克・加洛
Then to Frank Gallo.
愿他安息
May he rest in peace.
我跟他们说我不干了  我退出
I told them I was done. No more, out.
第二天晚上  罗杰・夏皮罗派来五个
Next night, Roger Shapiro sent five of my friends
我的伙计  对我做了一样的事
to do the same thing to me.
你愿意出庭作证吗
You're willing to testify to that in court.
绝不  我作证  他们会给我谋杀罪
No way, I tell them that, they'll put me away for murder.
-你已经在监狱了  -但刑期只有七年
- You're already away. - Yeah, for seven more years.
把这事告诉他们  我就是无期了
I tell them this, they'll put me away for life.
我要是能为你争取到豁免权呢
What if I can get you immunity?
-你无法保证  -没错
- You can't promise me that. - No, I can't.
但如果你为我这么做  我绝不会
But if you did this for me, there's no way
让他们判你谋杀罪
I'm gonna let them convict you for murder.
我凭什么相信你
Why should I believe you?
和你应该出庭作证的理由一样
For the same reason you need to take that stand.
我理解男人对女儿的爱
I know what it's like to have a daughter.
我也知道你和迈克・罗斯签协议
And I know you cut that deal with Mike Ross
就是为了让她原谅你
so that she'd forgive you.
但仅仅如此还不足以让她原谅你
But she needs more than that to forgive you.
她需要知道她父亲是个好人
She needs to know her father is a good man.
-我不是好人  -也许如此
- I'm not a good man. - Yeah, maybe not.
但如果你出庭  告诉世界你的所作所为
But if you got up there and told the world what you did,
阻止了那群禽兽再继续犯罪...
and stopped these monsters from ever doing it again--
让她看到这样的你  她一定会原谅你
you let her see that-- she'll forgive you.
我以自己的女儿起誓
And I swear on my own daughter,
我不会让你失望
I will not let you go down for it.
好
Okay.
我答应
I'll do it.
丹妮斯・加洛吗
Denise Gallo?
你是谁
Who are you?
认识你父亲的一个人
Someone who knew your father.
他  要我把这个给你
He, uh, wanted you to have this.
我想告诉你
I want you to know,
他是个好人
he was a decent man.
我想我终于理解
I believe I just figured out
你为什么这么喜欢这里了
why you fancy this place so much.
-为什么  -色调  烛光
- Why's that? - Colors and the candle light.
它们的衬托让你更帅了
They make you look tremendously handsome.
阿加德医生  要不是我了解你
Dr. Agard, if I didn't know better,
会以为你在搭讪我了
I'd think you were hitting on me.
要不是你了解我
If you didn't know better,
我也不会有机会在这里
I never would've gotten the chance.
-那是什么  -一个看到它让我想起了你的
- What's that? - It's just a little something
小东西
I saw that made me think of you.
-而且  -而且什么
- And-- - And what?
今天是我们恋爱两个月纪念日
It's our two month anniversary.
我不想搞的太隆重
I didn't want to make a big deal out of it.
而且我也没有说
And I certainly don't expect you to
-你必须记得  只是...  -宝拉  我当然记得
- to have remembered, but-- - Paula, of course I remembered.
不然你以为我为什么带了这个
Why do you think I got you this?
这是你公寓的钥匙
That's the key to your apartment.
没错
Yes, it is.
你真贴心
This is incredibly sweet.
但这也骗不到我
But it isn't gonna fool me into believing
你根本不知道
that you had the faintest notion
今天是我们两个月纪念日吧
it was our two month anniversary.
没错  我确实不知道  但是...
You're right. I didn't. But...
我本来就打算今晚给你的
I was gonna give you these tonight, anyway.
其实仔细想想
Which, if you think about it,
这不是更特别了吗
makes it even more special.
纪念日快乐  宝拉
Happy anniversary, Paula.
纪念日快乐  哈维
Happy anniversary, Harvey.
瑞秋・赞恩
希望你一个人也玩得愉快
你值得拥有最好的
我不是很确定你会来
I--I didn't know if you'd come.
对不起  马克
I'm sorry, Mark.
我做不到
I can't do this.
我不是很确定你会来
I didn't know if you'd come.
我怎么会不来
How could I not?